(Sheldon:)Hello, Stuart.
(Stuart:)Oh, hey, Sheldon.
Can I help you find something today?
(Sheldon:)No, I was just sitting at home...
(Sheldon:)...thinking about how it might be nice
to catch up with my ninth-favorite person.
- Ninth?
- You moved up one.
(Sheldon:)My pen pal in Somalia
was kidnapped by pirates.
(Sheldon:)So, uh, how are you?
(Stuart:)Uh, not so good.
My shrink just killed himseIf...
(Stuart:)...and blamed me in the note.
(Sheldon:)Great, great.
(Sheldon:)So, what's new with your family?
How's your mother? Ls she alive?
(Sheldon:)Yeah.
- Your father. Alive?
- Yes.
- How about your grandparents, they alive?
- No.
(Sheldon:)Oh, I'm so sorry for your loss.
(Sheldon:)On a cheerier note, I have a teeth-cleaning
appointment this afternoon.
(Sheldon:)What do you say you take me over there,
buddy boy?